Preliminary Guide to the Frank Bardacke Papers M2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 5: Media
  - (Copy) Phillip Vera Cruz 7/20/78 Side 2 by McBane, Topkins, Winegarden, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 45, Audiocassette 23)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 11/22/80 Tape 1 [7?], La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 1)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 3/24/78 Tape 1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 2)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 3/24/78 Tape 2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 3)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 3/24/78 Tape 3, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 4)
  - The Game Group 9/26/77 Tape 3, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 5)
  - Synanon Game at La Paz tape #2 5/3/77, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 6)
  - Synanon Game at La Paz tape #1 5/3/77, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 7)
  - The Game La Paz #1 7/7/77, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 8)
  - Phone Conversation, Cesar [Chavez] re: Tony Orendain 1976 [further notes on J-card], La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 9)
  - National Executive Board Plan Meeting 12/8/80 #1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 10)
  - National Executive Board Meeting June 15-17 1978 3/2 discuss on Philosophy #5, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 11)
  - National Executive Board Planning Meeting 12-8-80 #2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 12)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 11-22-80 Tape 8, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 13)
  - Discussion on the Game Tape 1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 14)
  - Discussion on the Game Tape 2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 15)
  - Discussion on the Game Tape 3, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 16)
  - Discussion on the Game Tape 4, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 17)
  - Discussion on the Game Tape 5, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 18)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 2nd Day (3/24/78), La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 19)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 4/4/78 #4 [5 on j-card], La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 20)
  - The Game, La Paz #2 7/7/77, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 46, Audiocassette 21)
  - Fred Ross interviewed by Anne Lofts in Alameda March 22,1982 Part 1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 1)
  - Fred Ross interviewed by Anne Lofts in Alameda March 22,1982 [Part 2?], La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 2)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 4/4/78 #1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 3)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 4/4/78 #2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 4)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 4/4/78 #3, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 5)
  - National Executive Board Meeting 4/4/78 #4, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 6)
  - Prime Time 1-5-80, 1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 7)
  - Prime Time 1-5-80, 2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 8)
  - Prime Time 1-5-80, 3, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 9)
  - National Executive Board Meeting June 15-17, 1978 Tape 2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 10)
  - National Executive Board Meeting June 15-17, 1978 Tape 1. Philosophy of Union. 3/2 Discuss on Philosophy #1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 11)
  - National Executive Board Meeting June 15-17, 1978 Tape 3. 3/2 Discuss on Philosophy #3, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 12)
  - The Game Group 7 9/26/77 Tape 2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 13)
  - Admin Off Management 12/31/77 Tape 1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 14)
  - The Game 9/26/77 Tape 1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 15)
  - Hartnell College National Executive Board Meeting 1, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 16)
  - Hartnell College National Executive Board Meeting 2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 17)
  - Hartnell College [National Executive Board Meeting] 3, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 18)
  - National Executive Board 3/11/79 Tape one, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 19)
  - National Executive Board 3/11/79 Tape two, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 20)
  - National Executive Board 3/11/79 Tape three, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 21)
  - The Game, 7-7-77 La Paz #3, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 47, Audiocassette 22)
  - CD: M0812 Box 35 Tape 1 Track 1; Track 2 [Fred Ross], 24 (Box 48, Audiocassette 1)
  - National Executive Board Meeting June 15-17, 1978 #4 Discussion on Philosophy #4, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 2)
  - Admin Office Management 12/31/1977 Tape 2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 3)
  - Admin Office Management 12/31/1977 Tape 3, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 4)
  - Admin Office Management 12/31/1977 Tape 4, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 5)
  - Admin Office Management 12/31/1977 Tape 5, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 6)
  - UFW Paid Rep. Conference 5/19/80 - 5/21/80, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 7)
  - UFW Paid Rep. Conference 5/19-5/21/80 Tape 2, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 8)
  - UFW Paid Rep. Conference 5/30/80 Tape 1 Reel 3, La Paz Tapes; 2 CD-Rs (Box 48, Audiocassette 9)
  - UFW Paid Rep. Conference 5/30/80 Tape 2 Reel 3, box from Ignacio; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 10)
  - Cesar [Chavez?] Interview Aug. 25, 1974, box from Ignacio; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 11)
  - Cesar [Chavez?] and Father [Librado Chavez?], box from Ignacio; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 12)
  - Discussion of Growers, Organizing, Exports tape 4, box from Ignacio; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 13)
  - Castryon Family Spanish Conversation. Susan Drake, box from Ignacio; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 14)
  - Castryon Family Translation. Susan Drake, box from Ignacio; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 15)
  - Devon McFarland, UFW Organizer Oct. 12, 1975; Charles Wollenberg on California agri-business Oct. 1, 1974. Susan Drake, box from Ignacio; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 16)
  - Conversation with 3 Farm Workers in Watsonville Jan. 19, 1977. Susan Drake, box from Ignacio; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 17)
  - [Janis The Latest?], box from Ignacio; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 18)
  - Lupe Sanchez [Wyne Sarchey?], box from Ignacio; audiocassette (Box 48, Audiocassette 19)
  - EPI July 03; [Hermilo] Mojica? Jul 8/03, 24 (Box 48, Audiocassette 20)
  - [Hermilo] Mojica 1 11/25/02, 24 (Box 48, Audiocassette 21)
  - Chayo Pelayo May 20, 2004, 24 (Box 48, Audiocassette 22)
  - [Hermilo] Mojica 8/1/05, 24 (Box 48, Audiocassette 23)